[METAL THUMPlNG]
[♪♪♪]
HANK:
All right, everybody. Listen up.
Tuco Salamanca.
For those of you
who were not with us
this morning
we raided his headquarters.
Also his last-known address.
Even the little den of iniquity
he keeps for his meth-hag girlfriend.
We netted a bunch
of his lieutenants.
The big man himself
smelled us coming.
So study the face.
Study the file.
Get a big old raging hard-on
at the idea of catching
this piece of shit.
[PEOPLE CHUCKLE]
My apologies
to the H.R. department.
Grow tumescent with anticipation.
All right.
On the hit parade, 1 998.
Reputed to have whacked
one "Dog" Paulson
back when our
homegrown bandidos
were wresting the crank trade
away from the So Cal biker gangs.
Also, we' re pretty sure
he knifed a Mexican national in '03.
And for my money, seeing how
he customarily deals with rivals,
I'd say he is a prime suspect
in the disappearance
of our dearly missed Krazy-8.
Hats over your heart
for that dirtball.
We hauled Tuco in
for questioning on that
but as usual,
we couldn't make it stick.
Yeah, he runs a tight ship.
Smug bastard.
And even worse,
El Paso says he' s got
some kind of cartel connection.
Yeah, yeah. I know it's...
We all know what's going on
down there.
We sure as hell don' t want it
going on up here,
which brings us to the good news.
We finally got some actual,
honest-to-God evidence.
This is one of Tuco's henchmen.
Street name: No-Doze.
Found him tucked in the junkyard
along with Tuco's own brother-in-law,
a.k.a. Gonzo.
Gonzo, this rocket scientist,
was moving No-Doze's body--
Either hiding it there
or pulling it out.
We' re still not sure.
--when he got his arm
crushed clean off.
Heh, heh.
Anyone wanna see the photos,
they' re on my website.
Hilarious.
Anyway. The upshot is
we got us a nice, big, juicy,
bloody fingerprint
which belongs to
Señor Tuco.
Christmas came early
to the Schrader household.
That is,
provided we find this guy.
So to all present, I ask you,
you wanna find this guy?
MAN 1 : Yes.
MAN 2: Yes.
What the hell was that? Jesus.
Wanna try that again?
Do you wanna find this guy?
AGENTS: Yes!
Are we going to find this guy?
Louder, damn it!
AGENTS: Yes!
Give me a "hell, yeah!"
AGENTS: Hell, yeah!
Hell, yeah!
ALL [CHANTlNG]:
Hell, yeah. Hell, yeah, Hell, yeah.
They ain't gonna find him.
Guy is in México by now.
Appearances, Gomey.
Tsk, tsk.
It's all about appearances.
Listen, l gotta take
some personal time.
Now, in the middle of a manhunt?
Skyler called last night.
It's Walt. He' s missing.
Just disappeared from the house,
and no one's heard from him since.
Damn. You don't think he...?
Holler if you need me.
All right.
Thanks a lot, man.
Appreciate that.
SKYLER:
This is the most recent photo.
We haven't taken many lately, so...
But that's what
he looks like now.
Without the hair.
[DOOR OPENS]
HANK:
Hey, it's me.
Hey, Tim.
Really appreciate you
sparing us your day off.
No worries.
Happy to help.
Yeah, this is helpful.
Good.
What about height and weight?
Five eleven,
most recently, about 1 70.
One sixty-five.
That's what l weigh.
I guess he weighs
a little less.
That's fine.
That's close enough.
Good.
What about other
distinguishing features?
Tattoos or moles or scars?
Anything that might help us.
Tattoos? No. Not really. No.
That's fine.
Is that the list of medications?
Yes.
I wrote them all down.
And there's no drug interactions.
None that are listed.
I called his doctor, so, no.
Has he been depressed?
He's, um, been withdrawn lately.
A little withdrawn.
Yeah.
Last night, he was, uh, agitated.
Agitated?
Yeah.
When he came home last night,
he was agitated, upset.
TIM:
Upset in general?
Or upset because
of something particular?
Um...
When I asked him
what was wrong,
he said:
"I don't know where to begin."
Then he just walked
out of the room--
Out of the bathroom.
I was in the tub,
I was taking a bath.
--and when l came out
about 1 0 minutes later,
he was gone.
Nothing else missing?
His keys, wallet, cell phone.
Just what was on him.
But-- What about the phone call?
Uh-- I' m looking into it.
What phone call?
Walt's cell phone rang.
He pulled it out,
looked at it,
and didn't answer it.
But then, a short time after,
he wandered
out of the bathroom.
I mean,
couldn't that be, uh,
important, right?
Anything else
you can think of?
Anything else. Um...
No. I called
the credit card providers,
and there's no report
of any recent activity.
I-- Let' s see.
I checked with every hospital
within 50 miles.
Every police station.
Every morgue.
So, no, I really don't--
I don't have anything else.
I was actually hoping
that you had something else,
being that you're the expert.
I'm sorry.
No worries.
I think this is
good enough to start.
Gives us plenty to work on.
Mrs. White.
Thank you.
Walter.
So that cell-phone call
she' s talking about?
I ran it.
And?
Never happened.
No record of it.
Second cell phone.
Yeah. l'm thinking.
[THUMPlNG ON METAL]
[MAN GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪]
[COUGHlNG]
I understand.
Out.
JESSE:
Get away from me!
[JESSE GRUNTING]
Settle down, bitch.
JESSE:
You gonna shoot me, huh?
Shoot me in here!
I hope I bleed like a mother too!
That way, you have to clean it up!
[GASPING AND PANTING]
It's your ride, retard.
I ain't gotta clean jack.
Now get out.
Get up.
JESSE:
Oh, my God.
Don't do this, Tuco.
[THE WALKMEN'S
"RED MOON" PLAYS]
No more posters?
Walter Jr.'s making more.
Thank you, Marie.
I don't think
he'll hurt himself.
I mean, he just
doesn't strike me
as the type.
He'll turn up.
[MARlE SIGHS]
Okay, the whole tiara thing,
I just find it bewildering that
Marie.
you didn't believe that--
Not now.
[MAN SPEAKlNG IN SPANlSH
ON TV]
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Empty your pockets.
Thought your name
was Heisenberg,
"Walter Hartwell White."
Heisenberg is kind of
a pseudonym.
You know, a business name.
Yeah.
I like doing business
with a family man.
There's always
a lot of collateral.
[TUCO LAUGHlNG]
Answer me one thing.
Can I trust you?
Yes. Yes, absolutely.
TUCO:
Sit down.
DEA...
hit my place of business
this morning.
About a hundred cops
looking for me.
You two haven't
been talking, right?
No.
Picked up my whole crew,
top to bottom.
Everybody except Gonzo.
That's weird, right?
I mean, don' t you think
that that's weird?
It's weird. Yes.
Unusual.
Last two days,
I couldn't get Gonzo
on the phone.
He's been acting all pouty
on account of No-Doze.
Explain to me.
How is it my fault that
that little bitch
did not know his place?
I saw this coming.
I can see the future, you know?
It's this gift that I have
deep inside my head.
I knew last night they were
gonna come try and bust me.
Gonzo.
He went and snitched
to the cops!
That lousy son of a bitch!
I trusted him like a brother!
I was good to him!
I was good!
I see Gonzo,
I'm gonna gut him,
I'm gonna skin him,
and l'm gonna stuff his hide
for a heavy bag,
and every time I hit him,
it' s going to be like
a lesson to myself!
You never,
never trust the people
that you love!
So you plan to ice Gonzo,
like, future tense?
What?
You' re saying, Tuco...
You' re saying that Gonzo
is currently operating
as a police informant
as far as you know?
I'm very sorry to hear that.
That's disappointing.
Yeah.
I'd waste him too, yo.
Shut up.
Okay.
They' re out there
looking for me right now.
They got ghetto birds
and black ops.
I need to get high. Oh, fu--
I need to get good and high.
[GRUNTS]
What's with this gak?
It smells like headcheese.
No, it' s, uh-- It' s killer.
Yeah, seriously.
So l was thinking
last night.
I came up with
this great idea.
México.
Mexico?
Ha, ha.
We' ll disappear
way out in the jungle.
We' ll set you up in a superlab.
We' ll do nothing but cook 24/7.
And no Federales
are gonna mess with us
because l got my people there.
Connections.
We' re going to make
beaucoup bucks,
Heisenberg, huh?
Tuco, I...
I have a wife and family.
So what?
You' ll get another one.
I don't want you to take
this the wrong way,
but I can't just
uproot my life like that.
Yeah, man.
I mean, me neither.
Who's talking to you?
JESSE:
You need me, man,
because l cooked that scante
in your hands.
Yeah.
I'll tell you something, yo.
You never tried nothing like it.
Stink or no stink,
one bump,
you' ll be flying high for days.
It's a new product him
and l've been working up.
Careful when you hit it.
It kicks like a 1 2 gauge
when it comes on.
[CHUCKLES]
It's got a
secret ingredient.
What secret ingredient?
Chili powder.
I hate chili powder.
This blue magic, this is money.
You keep cooking this,
Heisenberg.
We' re gonna rewrite
history with this.
[GRUNTS
THEN LAUGHS]
All right. Time to clean
the menudo out from
between your ears.
No, no, no. No,
I need him, Tuco.
I need him very, very badly.
He's my partner.
And if he doesn' t go,
I don't go.
I'll tell you this.
My cousins are driving
up here right now
to smuggle us back down,
and they're gonna be here
by sunset
and you're gonna be
on that truck,
or you're gonna be dead!
And you...
You better hope they got room
in the trunk.
SKYLER:
Where are you going?
Louis is taking me
to the train station.
We' ll put these up.
No, no, honey. No, l'll do it.
He wants to help, let him help.
I mean,
how long has it been
since you' ve slept?
Yeah, she's right, Sky.
Why don' t you lay down
a while?
For Christ sake,
you got a bun in the oven.
I got my cell if you need me.
Okay?
SKYLER: Okay.
Bye, sweetie. I' ll see you later.
WALT JR.: All right. Bye.
Actually, I think the very fact
they haven't found him yet
bodes well.
Well, l mean, if he--
You know.
Somebody would' ve
smelled something by now.
There's got to be
something.
Some detail that
we haven't picked up on.
What about the second cell phone?
Ah, Jesus.
What?
We can't just ignore
a potential clue, Hank.
Okay.
What are you talking about?
Uh, the call you said Walt got
before he disappeared?
There's no record of it
with the phone company.
No incoming,
no dropped calls,
nothing.
But his phone rang.
I heard it.
Um, all right.
Well, then if that's the case,
he must have a second phone.
Wh-- Why?
What sense would
there be in that?
Yeah. All right. Okay.
I'm not here to argue with you.
No, Hank.
You can't just bring up secret
cell phone and then drop it.
What does it mean?
I don't know, Sky.
What do you want me to say?
It means Walt has a secret.
Everyone's got one from somebody,
big or little.
Okay. Oh, wow. Everyone. Okay.
Skyler, come on.
He kept cancer
from you for weeks.
Okay, then, let's assume
there's a second cell phone.
So what?
What, is he having an affair?
Walt? Please.
What about the marijuana?
He's not on pot anymore.
Says who? Him?
Chemotherapy and
marijuana go together
like apple pie
and Chevrolet.
Maybe he' s addicted
to the pot
and he owes
his drug dealer
a lot of money.
Marie, you don't
get hooked on pot
like that.
How do you know?
You didn't even know he
had a second cell phone.
Hank, you have to question
this drug-dealer person.
He may know something.
Well, l'm telling you,
we're grasping at straws here.
Then grasp.
HANK:
Excuse me, ma' am.
Hi, l'm looking for Jesse.
He around?
No. I'm afraid not.
Why?
I'm sorry. Hank Schrader.
I'm actually hoping
to talk to Jesse about
my brother-in-law, Walter White.
He taught your son
chemistry in high school.
Oh, Mr. White.
Yes, l remember him.
That was a long time ago.
Yes, ma'am.
It's my understanding
that he and Jesse,
they' ve stayed in touch.
Really?
Yeah.
Huh.
Mr. White must' ve seen
some potential in Jesse.
He really tried
to motivate him.
He was one of the
few teachers who cared.
Yeah, Walt's that way.
He's a good man.
I'm so sorry to hear
about his illness.
Please pass along
our best wishes.
I certainly will,
as soon as he turns up.
He's missing, actually.
Just kind of walked off, or...
Anyway, which is why
I'm going around,
trying to think of anyone
who knows him, even slightly.
That's terrible.
Anything we can do to help.
Well, if you could put me
in touch with your son...
Like l said,
we're kind of desperate for leads.
Jesse's not answering either
phone number I have for him,
and no one seems to be home
at his house.
And why do you think my son
and Mr. White would be in touch?
I don't necessarily.
I just, um--
Are you with the police?
No, ma'am. Not at all.
I'm with the
Drug Enforcement Administration.
Oh, my God.
Is my son in trouble?
I have absolutely no reason
to think that, no.
Do I need to get a lawyer?
You know, you don't seem
very forthright about this,
coming here and
asking questions
about my son and--
Mrs. Pinkman, I swear to you,
I'm not here on official capacity.
I do not care what your son may
or may not have done wrong.
I just wanna find
my brother-in-law.
His wife is worried sick,
and she's got a baby
on the way.
I'm sorry.
I would like to help you,
but I have not seen my son
in over a month.
I don't expect to see him
anytime soon.
Well, thanks for your time.
Oh, uh...
If you could tell me
one more thing.
Is Jesse still driving the
'89 Chevy Monte Carlo,
as far as you know?
If he had spent half
as much time and money
on his education
as he has on that
ridiculous bouncing car...
Low rider, huh?
Gomey, hey.
No, nothing yet. Hey, listen,
do me a solid and check out
a '89 Chevy Monte Carlo
registered to a one
Jesse Pinkman.
Specifically, l wanna know
if the car' s got a LoJack.
It's one of those jack-off low riders,
so l'm betting it' s got a good shot
that there is.
If so, can you go ahead
and get me a fix on it?
Thanks, buddy.
[MAN & WOMAN SPEAKlNG
IN SPANISH ON TV]
[GRUNTlNG]
Chili powder.
Did I not already tell you
how moronic that was?
Whatever, man.
At least
I tried something.
Hey, it almost worked too.
How's about
you leaving my gun, huh?
First you boost it, then
you leave it in your house.
My gun.
How was l supposed to know
you were chauffeuring Tuco
to my doorstep?
Well, at least
he wants you alive.
[NEWSCASTER SPEAKING
IN SPANISH ON TV]
[MAN SINGlNG AND
MUSIC PLAYING ON TV]
Hey, I don't get it.
If Tuco didn't kill Gonzo,
then who did?
I don't know.
Does it really matter?
If he finds out that
Gonzo is dead and
not a police informant,
who does he
automatically blame?
Us.
We need a plan.
Think, think.
Let's just bum-rush him, man.
You know,
you crack him over
the head with something,
and l'll go for his gun.
[THUD]
Crack him over the head
with something?
Hey, you got the C-bomb,
man, all right?
You' re as good
as checked out already.
Okay? You should be,
like, all sacrificial,
jumping on a grenade, yo.
Just...
Oh, so my life
is not the priority here
because l'm gonna be
dead soon anyway.
That's your point?
Uh, yeah.
We gotta get him to take this.
Well, he don't much like
the taste of chili P.
That much
has been established.
So unless
you can convince him
to booty bump...
Eat. We got a long ride
ahead of us.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Go on, sit.
You' re looking a little weak,
Heisenberg.
I don't want you to go belly up
before we get there.
TUCO:
Take it easy, Tio.
I will feed you.
I eat first. That' s the deal.
What?
[LAUGHING]
I get it, I get it, I get it.
Oh, you greedy old bastard.
I tell you, Heisenberg.
Old people.
You feed them, huh?
You put them
in a really nice crib
in the country,
and yet they gotta steal
the food off your plate.
You better eat every bite of that.
TUCO:
What did you do that for?
God!
[TUCO SPEAKING lN SPANlSH]
[RAPlD GUNFIRE]
Ha, ha, ha. Shh.
Hey, look. Look.
There's nothing left.
[BELL DINGlNG]
[TUCO GRUNTS]
What?
What do you want?
No.
Don't even tell me
that you' re hungry.
Don't go there.
[LAUGHS]
Are you mad-dogging them, Tio?
What, you don't like them?
One ding.
That means yes.
Tio don't like you.
Why don' t you like them, Tio?
You don't trust them?
Why don' t you trust them, Tio?
Tuco, come on. He's...
There clearly some dementia.
He's not lucid.
Shh.
Did they do something
to you, Tio?
Something that you don't like?
What did they do to you?
What did you do to my tio?
Nothing. Nothing.
Bullshit! My tio does not lie!
I don't know.
I swear.
I don't know. l--
No, I-- Maybe it was--
I did change the channel
on his TV, but...
Yeah, that's it.
While you were cooking,
he was watching
one of those, um--
Those telenovels
with all those ripe honeys on it.
He was really into it.
I told you not to
change the channel, man.
You know,
dude needs his eye candy.
That's it.
[LAUGHING]
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
Is that it, Tio?
Did they change your mamitas?
What are you telling me, Tio?
Huh?
Are they punking me?
JESSE:
Hey. No.
No, man. No.
Come here! Aah!
No.
No, no, Tuco.
[JESSE GRUNTING]
Tuco, no. Tuco.
Tuco.
Shut up!
No. Please, no. God.
Please, no.
No, God.
I don't wanna die.
Tell me what you did,
Walter!
JESSE:
Jesus, I don't wanna die.
No!
Tell me what you did!
We tried to poison you.
We tried to poison you,
because you're an insane,
degenerate piece of filth,
and you deserve to die.
[GRUNTlNG]
[SCREAMlNG]
Who's the bitch now?
[GROANING]
[CRYING]
Let him bleed.
The keys.
Tuco.
Oh, my God.
WALT:
The cousins?
[♪♪♪]
[TUCO GRUNTING]
JESSE:
What the hell is going on?
Jesse Pinkman.
You' re a hard man to find.
Oh, shit.
Easy.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God. Hank.
Who?
Hank.
What?
Oh, my God.
Stay. What are you doing?
[BELL DINGlNG]
[♪♪♪]